[
  {
    "category": "Acting Resume",
    "question": "What actress starred in the films Watchmen, Couples Retreat and The Heartbreak Kid?",
    "answer": "Malin Akerman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "question": "The Gold Glove award is presented each year to the best defensive player at each position. Within 3 either way, what is the record for the most Gold Gloves won by a single player? (2PT BONUS FOR EXACT)",
    "answer": "18 (15 - 21) - Greg Maddux",
    "range": true
  },
  {
    "category": "HTQ",
    "question": "What are the four LEAST populated U.S. state capitals? (Municipal area only) (2PT BONUS FOR ALL) ",
    "answer": "1. Montpelier - 7,800  2. Pierre - 3,646  3. Augusta - 19,136   4. Frankfort - 25,52"
  },
  {
    "category": "FQ",
    "question": "Within 7 either way, what is te record for the most diferent countries visited by a sitting U.S. president? (Unique nations, not total trips)",
    "answer": "58 (51 - 65) - Obama"
  }, {
    "category": "Acting Resume",
    "question": "What actress starred in the films Watchmen, Couples Retreat and The Heartbreak Kid?",
    "answer": "Malin Akerman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "question": "The Gold Glove award is presented each year to the best defensive player at each position. Within 3 either way, what is the record for the most Gold Gloves won by a single player? (2PT BONUS FOR EXACT)",
    "answer": "18 (15 - 21) - Greg Maddux",
    "range": true
  },
  {
    "category": "HTQ",
    "question": "What are the four LEAST populated U.S. state capitals? (Municipal area only) (2PT BONUS FOR ALL) ",
    "answer": "1. Montpelier - 7,800  2. Pierre - 3,646  3. Augusta - 19,136   4. Frankfort - 25,52"
  },
  {
    "category": "FQ",
    "question": "Within 7 either way, what is te record for the most diferent countries visited by a sitting U.S. president? (Unique nations, not total trips)",
    "answer": "58 (51 - 65) - Obama"
  }, {
    "category": "Acting Resume",
    "question": "What actress starred in the films Watchmen, Couples Retreat and The Heartbreak Kid?",
    "answer": "Malin Akerman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "question": "The Gold Glove award is presented each year to the best defensive player at each position. Within 3 either way, what is the record for the most Gold Gloves won by a single player? (2PT BONUS FOR EXACT)",
    "answer": "18 (15 - 21) - Greg Maddux",
    "range": true
  },
  {
    "category": "HTQ",
    "question": "What are the four LEAST populated U.S. state capitals? (Municipal area only) (2PT BONUS FOR ALL) ",
    "answer": "1. Montpelier - 7,800  2. Pierre - 3,646  3. Augusta - 19,136   4. Frankfort - 25,52"
  },
  {
    "category": "FQ",
    "question": "Within 7 either way, what is te record for the most diferent countries visited by a sitting U.S. president? (Unique nations, not total trips)",
    "answer": "58 (51 - 65) - Obama"
  }, {
    "category": "Acting Resume",
    "question": "What actress starred in the films Watchmen, Couples Retreat and The Heartbreak Kid?",
    "answer": "Malin Akerman"
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "question": "The Gold Glove award is presented each year to the best defensive player at each position. Within 3 either way, what is the record for the most Gold Gloves won by a single player? (2PT BONUS FOR EXACT)",
    "answer": "18 (15 - 21) - Greg Maddux",
    "range": true
  },
  {
    "category": "HTQ",
    "question": "What are the four LEAST populated U.S. state capitals? (Municipal area only) (2PT BONUS FOR ALL) ",
    "answer": "1. Montpelier - 7,800  2. Pierre - 3,646  3. Augusta - 19,136   4. Frankfort - 25,52"
  },
  {
    "category": "FQ",
    "question": "Within 7 either way, what is te record for the most diferent countries visited by a sitting U.S. president? (Unique nations, not total trips)",
    "answer": "58 (51 - 65) - Obama"
  }
]